What's wrong with you?
You should be asking what you did.
Who are you really?
What do you mean?
Why pretend to be a Nanny?
It's a misunderstanding.
Don't move.
That's impossible.
You've always been here.
Face reality.
Running away won't solve anything.
The Nanny was here.
You tricked her into leaving.
That's not true.
There, there. Don't cry, baby.
What the hell are you doing?
What are you doing?
Why did Lu Yuan ask you to come?
Get the hell out.
Get the hell out, Mrs. Lu!
Mrs. Lu! Mrs. Lu! I'm sorry.
You only make things worse for me.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Mommy's here.
Where are you right now?
Don't be afraid.
Don't blame me.
It was just an accident.
You're just an illusion.
So the real Jiang Jia...
isn't Lu Yuan's lover.
That was just your fear all along.
So she isn't a real Nanny either.
She said...
she's Sun Hui's girlfriend.
But if Sun Hui really recommended her...
then what about Auntie Liu?
Lu Yuan couldn't have hired two Nannies.
You can verify this with Lu Yuan.
And then what?
Then tell him...
I killed someone.
Looks like I'll have to get the answers from her.
Are you really going to call the police?
I can't drag Lu Yuan into this.
What about Xiao Ran?
Doing this means abandoning her.
Mommy, don't leave me.
Hey, Lu Yuan.
The Nanny just contacted me.
What did she say?
She said you fired her.
And mentioned you're not doing too well.
Don't listen to her.
But you said she was great before,
and planned to keep her.
I asked the Nanny.
You two hadn't even met yet,
or spoken on the phone.
That was just a misunderstanding.
It's hard to explain over the phone.
I just wanted to let you know,
filming on set is almost done.
I'll wrap things up with the crew and head home.
It's okay.
It's the first day of filming.
Make sure nothing goes wrong.
Nothing is more important than you.
Actually, ever since I left the house,
I've been blaming myself.
I shouldn't have left you at a time like this.
You've already done enough.
Not enough.
Wait for me to get home.
Actually, Lu Yuan
is already very anxious.
He just doesn't want you to worry.
I know.
Whatever you decide to do,
you need to act fast.
Mommy, hurry!
I'm sorry, I can't help you.
Then shut up.
Don't make things worse for me.
This isn't a long-term solution.
I'll handle it as soon as possible.